

CONTACT

+48 884 855 028 nataliaelamuzyka@gmail.com Lublin <u>LinkedIn</u>

IT PROJECT

Product Page Redesign

<u>Link</u>:https://www.behance.net/gallery/177371 047/electro-Case-Study

The project entailed a complete redesign of the website for an electronics retail store. Following the redesign, the purchasing process was subjected to testing with the intended user base.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Figma/Marvel/Canva
- Miro
- Confluence
- JIRA
- Google Analytics,
- HTML + CSS
- UX Workshops
- · UX Research

LANGUAGES

- Polish native
- English C2
- Russian B1

SOFT SKILLS

- · Design Thinking
- Public Relation
- · Team player

NATALIA MUZYKA

UX DESIGNER

I'm a newbie UX designer, but I've just wrapped up my first project.

During my work I utilize my psychological and PR background.

My creativity and ability to think empathetically allow me to create products that not only meet users' needs, but also create satisfying and memorable experiences.

EDUCATION

UX/UI Designer

Software Development Academy | 03.2023 - currently

- Validation: User Interviews, Usage Tracking
- Creating Mock-ups
- Information Architecture:
- Emphathizing: Journey Map, Persona, Empathy Map
- Getting to Know the User: Google Analytics, In-Depth Interviews, Surveys
- Gathering Business Requirements: Business Model Canvas; Value Proposition Canvas

Personal Branding & Public Relations

Collegium Humanum | Postgraduate | 02.2023 - currently

English Studies

Academy of Economics and Humanities | Master | 02.2021 - 07.2023

Psychology

SWPS University | Bachelor | 10.2017 - 10.2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern in IT

Concentrix | 07.2023 - currently

 Supporting documentation operations by creating, editing and organizing content, ensuring accuracy and collaborating with cross-functional teams.

Interpreter to Public Affairs Office

Atlas Advisors | 02.2022 - 03.2023

- Coordination interpreters for US Army units in Poland
- · Liaise with organizations
- Arrange meetings with authorities and interpret during official engagements

Interpreter to Public Affairs Office

Mission Essential | 08.2020 - 02.2022

- Support NATO units in Poland by:
 - Interpreting during meetings
 - O|rganizing promotional events
 - Providing written translations